Close Country Selector

### Are you looking for information about offers, devices or your account?

Please choose your local Vodafone website

#### Africa

* [Egypt (EN)](https://web.vodafone.com.eg/en/home "Egypt (EN)")
* [Tanzania (EN)](https://www.vodacom.co.tz/ "Tanzania (EN)")

#### Asia Pacific

#### Europe

No thanks, I want to stay on Vodafone.com

CountriesSearch

Privacy and Cookie Policy
=========================

Loading...

Welcome to Vodafone’s Privacy and Cookie Statement
--------------------------------------------------

This page provides information on how we use, collect, and share your personal data when you visit Vodafone.com. We understand this is a big responsibility and we work hard to protect your personal data. For more information, please see below our cookie and privacy statement.

To learn more about how Vodafone seeks to respect and protect the right to privacy, including our customers’ lawful rights to hold and express opinions and share information and ideas without interference, please visit our dedicated Privacy centre.

The Privacy and Cookie statements below are specifically in relation to your use of this website (Vodafone.com). Other Vodafone websites and applications are likely to have their own specific policies and we encourage you to check those websites and applications independently.

### Privacy statement

**Last updated: 18 March 2024**

In the following privacy policy "we/us" means Vodafone Group Plc; "third party" means someone who is not you or us; and "Vodafone Group" means Vodafone Group Plc and any company or other organisation in which Vodafone Group Plc owns more than 15% of the share capital.

Our registered office is Vodafone House, The Connection Newbury, Berkshire RG14 2FN. We are registered in England under company number 1833679. Vodafone Group Plc is registered with the Information Commissioner's Office (ICO), registration number Z8088474.

Changes to our Privacy Policy:

This Privacy Policy gets updated from time to time; whenever we make a change, we’ll post this on our website and ask you to review your privacy settings next time you come to visit vodafone.com

### Privacy policy

Personal information we collect about you

##### Information we collect about you

The types of information we collect about you when you visit and interact with this site are:

* Your contact details such as name and email address where you have contacted us through this site; or
* If you have agreed to cookies, data such as your site preferences or language settings. We can also use this information in an aggregate manner to understand how our visitors navigate this site so we can make it better.

##### When we collect your personal information

We collect your personal information when you:

* Browse and interact with the vodafone.com website; or
* Use our contact forms to get in touch or register your interest.

##### Vodafone will process your personal data based on:

1. Our legitimate business interests, for example, direct marketing and improvement of our services. Whenever we rely on this lawful basis to process your data, we assess our business interests to make sure they do not override your rights. Additionally, in some cases you have the right to object to this processing. For more information, visit the Your Rights section of this policy.
2. Consent you provide where Vodafone does not rely on another legal basis. Consent will always be presented separately to you, can be withdrawn at any time and you will be given details on how to change your mind.

How we use your personal information

##### Maintaining this website and providing you with any services requested through it

For example, when you contact us through this site, we’ll use your information to ensure you get the right information and response.

##### To personalise this website and track its performance

Because of the way this website operates, we may also use information from your browser or browsing activities to personalize the site or route you to relevant information. For example, we may use web-log information, cookies or web beacons in ways that help us maintain some of your site preferences, send you to the right country-specific information or understand how our visitors navigate the site so we can make it better.  
  
You can choose whether or not to allow cookies or web beacons using your browser preferences. To find out more about cookies and your choices, visit the Cookies section of this statement.

How we share your your personal information

Some of the services or information you can request on this site may come from other members of our corporate family. Therefore, we may share your information with other companies within Vodafone Group (for example, your local carrier). The laws of the countries where these companies are based may not be the same as those in the EU, but your information will be treated with the same high standard of care wherever it’s processed within the corporate family.

International data transfer

We may need to transfer your information to other Vodafone Group companies (for example, if the information you request is delivered by them) or service providers in countries outside the European Economic Area (EEA). The EEA consists of countries in the European Union, Switzerland, Iceland, Liechtenstein and Norway: they are considered to have equivalent laws when it comes to data protection and privacy. This kind of data transfer may happen if our servers (i.e. where we store data) or our suppliers and service providers are based outside the EEA, or if you use our services and products while visiting countries outside this area.  
  
If Vodafone sends your information to a country that is not in the EEA, we will make sure that your information is properly protected. We will always ensure that there is a proper legal agreement that covers the data transfer. In addition, if the country is not considered to have laws that are equivalent to EU data protection standards then we will implement additional technical security and organisational safeguards such as asking the third party to enter into a legal agreement that reflects those standards.

How long we keep your information for

We’ll store your information for as long as we have to by law. If there’s no legal requirement for us to retain the data, we’ll only store it for as long as we need to.

Keeping your personal information secure

We have specialised security teams who constantly review and improve our measures to protect your personal information from unauthorised access, accidental loss, disclosure or destruction.  
Communications over the internet (such as emails) aren’t secure unless they’ve been encrypted. Your communications may go through a number of countries before being delivered, as this is the nature of the internet.

We cannot accept responsibility for any unauthorised access or loss of personal information that is beyond our control.  
We’ll never ask for your secure personal or account information by an unsolicited means of communication. You’re responsible for keeping your personal and account information secure and not sharing it with others.

Our website may provide links to third-party websites. We cannot be responsible for the security and content of such third-party websites. So make sure you read that company’s privacy and cookies policies before using or putting your personal information on their site.

The same applies to any third-party websites or content you connect to using our products and services.  
You may choose to disclose your information in certain ways such as social plug-ins (including those offered by Google, Facebook, Twitter and Pinterest) or using third-party services that allow you to post reviews or other information publicly, and a third party could use that information.

Social plug-ins and social applications are operated by the social network themselves and are subject to their own terms of use and privacy and cookies policies. You should make sure you’re familiar with these.

Your rights

Under the law, you have a number of rights that you can exercise free of charge. We have included a summary of these below; if you would like to discuss or exercise any of these, please contact us through the details provided.

##### Right to correct personal data

If you believe any of the personal data we hold about you is incorrect, you can request we update it.

##### Right to access personal data

You have a right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you, and how it has been processed.

##### Right to data portability

In some circumstances, you have the right to receive the personal information about you which you have provided to us, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and have the right to transmit this data to a third party.

##### Right to object to use of personal data

In some circumstances, you can request that we temporarily suspend the processing of your data.

##### Right to erasure

In some circumstances, such as where we no longer have a justifiable reason to continue to process your data, you can request we delete it.

##### Right to restrict use of your data

If you feel data we hold on you is inaccurate or believe we shouldn’t be processing your data, please contact our Customer Services team to discuss your rights. In certain circumstances you will have the right to ask us to restrict processing.

##### How to lodge a complaint

If you have a complaint, you can contact us on the details provided. We’ll do our best to help but if you’re still unhappy, you can contact the ICO, which is the UK data protection regulator – their details are at [**www.ico.org.uk**](http://www.ico.org.uk./).

### Cookie policy

Our cookie policy

This cookie policy applies for cookies described below which may be placed when you visit different pages on the [**www.vodafone.com**](https://www.vodafone.com/) domain for example some may be set when you first visit [**www.vodafone.com**](https://www.vodafone.com/) and then additional cookies may be placed when you move around the website to subdomains for example [**www.vodafone.com/business**](https://www.vodafone.com/business). 

This cookie policy does not apply to subdomains of [**www.vodafone.com**](https://www.vodafone.com/) that contain its own cookie policy.

In this cookie policy we explain what cookies are, how we use them and how you can manage them for both our site and other websites you might use.

What are cookies

Cookies usually comprise of unique alphanumeric identifier that sits on your browser. In some cases, we won’t be able to link the information we collect by using a cookie back to you. They can, however, enable us to link that information back to you and your personal information, for example, when you log in, or choose to register for a service, or newsletter. We may also use cookies in order to provide you with personalised adverts based on your browsing behaviour.

If you want to know more about cookies, head to [**aboutcookies.org**](https://www.aboutcookies.org/). (Please note: This link opens a new window or browser tab).

How we use cookies

We use cookies to make our website work, or work more efficiently. We also use cookies to track what you've done on the site so we can understand what you like and use or don't like and don't use to provide a more enjoyable, customised service and experience, as well as to help us develop and deliver better content, products and services tailored to our customers' interests and needs.  
  
Our cookies don't hold personal information such as your name. They simply let us find information once you're logged in or help link your browsing information to you and your personal information when you choose to register for a service, white paper or newsletter.  
  
To do this we sometimes use persistent cookies. We take looking after your personal information seriously – we're always monitoring and improving how we protect it.  
  
We've put our cookies into the following categories, to make it easier for you to understand why we need them:

1. Strictly necessary – these are used to help make our website work efficiently and enable you to use our services and cannot be switched off.
2. Performance – these are used to analyse the way our website works and how we can improve it for example which pages you visit the most often and if you get any error messages from web pages;
3. Functionality – these help to enhance your experience by doing things like remembering choices you make and provide a more enhanced, personal features; and
4. Targeting/advertising – these are used to share some information with third parties who we advertise with, so we know how you've reached our website. We can also use cookies to identify the parts of the website you are interested in. We then use this information to show you adverts and pages we think may also be of interest to you, to tailor how we communicate with you, or to tailor the contents of the communications we send to you. If you prefer, you can opt out of these. Tailoring of content means it includes information reflecting the interest you’ve shown in the content of our web pages, or offers or promotions that we think may interest you, and to improve how we respond to your needs.
5. Persistent Cookies - We sometimes use persistent cookies as well as 'session-based' cookies. A 'persistent' cookie will remain for a period of time set for that cookie. A 'session-based' cookie is allocated only for the duration of your visit to our website and automatically expires when you close down your browser. **Please also note that some cookies may be set by your browser, for example when you browse using Google Chrome. We don’t control the use of browser cookies, so we suggest you check the browser’s cookie policy to understand how those are used and how you can manage them.**

| **Where it appears** | **What it’s called** | **What it’s used for** | **Type** | **Duration** |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Vodafone.com | OptanonConsent | This cookie is set by the cookie compliance solution from OneTrust. It stores information about the categories of cookies the site uses and whether visitors have given or withdrawn consent for the use of each category. This enables site owners to prevent cookies in each category from being set in the users browser, when consent is not given. The cookie has a normal lifespan of one year, so that returning visitors to the site will have their preferences remembered. It contains no information that can identify the site visitor. | 1   | 1 Years |
| Vodafone.com | \_vapi | Cookie that contains a session identifier used to authenticate the use and deliver different APIs | 1   | 0 Days |
| Vodafone.com | OptanonAlertBoxClosed | This cookie is set by websites using certain versions of the cookie law compliance solution from OneTrust. It is set after visitors have seen a cookie information notice and in some cases only when they actively close the notice down. It enables the website not to show the message more than once to a user. The cookie has a one year lifespan and contains no personal information. | 1   | 1 Years |
| Vodafone.com | JSESSIONID | General purpose platform session cookie, used by sites written in JSP. Usually used to maintain an anonymous user session by the server. | 1   | 0 Days |
| Vodafone.com | s\_fid | This cookie name is associated with the analytics service provided by Adobe's Site Catalyst product suite. It is a new cookie introduced in 2013 as a 'fallback' visitor identifier where the s\_vi cookie normally used for this purpose is blocked. It contains a randomly generated, unique id. | 2   | 5 Years |
| Vodafone.com | utag\_main | This cookie name is associated with the Tealium data platform and is used for web analytics. | 2   | 1 Years |
| Vodafone.com | \_gclxxxx | Google conversion tracking cookie | 2   | 3 Months |
| Vodafone.com | \_ga | This cookie name is associated with Google Universal Analytics - which is a significant update to Google's more commonly used analytics service. This cookie is used to distinguish unique users by assigning a randomly generated number as a client identifier. It is included in each page request in a site and used to calculate visitor, session and campaign data for the sites analytics reports. By default it is set to expire after 2 years, although this is customisable by website owners. | 2   | 2 Years |
| Vodafone.com | s\_sq | Adobe Site Catalyst cookie, stores information about the previous link clicked within the site | 2   | 0 Days |
| Vodafone.com | s\_cc | Adobe Site Catalyst cookie, determines whether cookies are enabled in the browser | 2   | 0 Days |
| Vodafone.com | ELOQUA | Eloqua Business Marketing platform - this cookie collects and transfers contact info from webforms to internal databases. | 3   | 1 Years |
| Vodafone.com | SITESJSESSIONID | cookie used for storing user session identifier in web applications | 3   | 0 Days |
| Vodafone.com | ln\_or | This is a LinkedIn cookie used to determine if Oribi analytics can be carried out on a specific domain | 4   | 0 Days |
| Vodafone.com | s\_ecid | This cookie is associated with the Adobe Audience Manager ID (DMP). This cookie sets a unique ID for the visitor, that allows third party advertisers to target the visitor with relevant advertisements. This pairing service is provided by third party advertisement hubs, which allows real-time bidding for advertisers. | 4   | 2 Years |
| Vodafone.com | \_fbp | Used by Facebook to deliver a series of advertisement products such as real time bidding from third party advertisers | 4   | 3 Months |
| Vodafone.com | AMCVS\_ | This is a pattern type cookie name associated with Adobe Marketing Cloud. It stores a unique visitor identifier, and uses an organisation identifier. | 4   | 0 Days |
| Vodafone.com | AMCV\_ | This is a pattern type cookie name associated with Adobe Marketing Cloud. It stores a unique visitor identifier, and uses an organisation identifier to allow a company to track users across their domains and services. | 4   | 2 Years |
| Vodafone.com | ELQSTATUS | Eloqua Business Marketing platform - this cookie is used to recognise unique visitors to website pages and to track the pages they visit. | 4   | 1 Years |
| Vodafone.com | ConsentSiteWideAlertBoxClosed | Onetrust Contains a copy of the OptanonAlertBoxClosed cookie. Used to track consent status across subdomains. | 1   | 1 Years |
| Vodafone.com | QueryStrings | Group Business - Campaign source tracking cookie | 4   | 0 Days |
| Vodafone.com | gpv\_pnp | Adobe Analytics A session cookie used for site analytics | 2   | 0 Days |
| Vodafone.com | ConsentSiteWide | Tealium - Used to support cookie consent | 1   | 1 Years |
| Vodafone.com | timestamp pageview | Tealium Cookie to track timestamp of pageview | 2   | 0 Days |
| Vodafone.com | VisitorServicesVisitorId | Oracle Contains an anonymous visitor ID for personalization within the Oracle WCS platform. | 4   | 4 Years |
| Vodafone.com | gpv\_pn | Adobe Analytics A session cookie used for site analytics | 2   | 0 Days |
| Vodafone.com | s\_campaign | Used to save campaign codes for analytics purposes | 2   | 0 Days |

Third party cookies

Third party cookies originate from a domain that’s different to the website being visited. For example, when you visit our website, we may link to another company's website – like our Facebook or Twitter account, or a video from our YouTube page.

So, when you 'Like' or 'Tweet' an item from our website, these sites may sometimes put cookies on your computer. We don't control how they use their cookies, so we suggest you check their website to see how they're using them and how you can manage them.

Affiliates of the Vodafone Group with a different domain name may also place cookies on our website, to show you adverts or pages of other Vodafone Group companies that may be of interest to you. Details of these affiliates – and how to opt-out – are included in the table.

Third parties that may put cookies on our website are

| **Host** | **Cookie Name** | **Description** | **Duration** | **Category** |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
| youtube.com | YSC | YouTube is a Google owned platform for hosting and sharing videos. YouTube collects user data through videos embedded in websites, which is aggregated with profile data from other Google services in order to display targeted advertising to web visitors across a broad range of their own and other websites. | 0 Days | 1   |
| www.vodafone.co.uk | TS01xxxxxxxx | TS  | 0 Days | 1   |
| www.vodafone.co.uk | TSxxxxxxxxxx | TS  | 0 Days | 1   |
| investors.vodafone.com | AWSALB | AWS ELB application load balancer | 6 Days | 1   |
| investors.vodafone.com | AWSALBCORS | This cookie is managed by AWS and is used for load balancing. | 6 Days | 1   |
| careers.vodafone.com | ppms\_privacy\_xxxxxx | This cookie name is associated with the Piwik open source web analytics platform. It is used to help website owners track visitor behaviour and measure site performance. It stores the visitor?s consent to data collection and usage. | 1 Years | 1   |
| careers.vodafone.com | OptanonConsent | This cookie is set by the cookie compliance solution from OneTrust. It stores information about the categories of cookies the site uses and whether visitors have given or withdrawn consent for the use of each category. This enables site owners to prevent cookies in each category from being set in the users browser, when consent is not given. The cookie has a normal lifespan of one year, so that returning visitors to the site will have their preferences remembered. It contains no information that can identify the site visitor. | 1 Years | 1   |
| careers.vodafone.com | OptanonAlertBoxClosed | This cookie is set by websites using certain versions of the cookie law compliance solution from OneTrust. It is set after visitors have seen a cookie information notice and in some cases only when they actively close the notice down. It enables the website not to show the message more than once to a user. The cookie has a one year lifespan and contains no personal information. | 1 Years | 1   |
| careers.vodafone.com | \_pk\_id.{id} | This cookie name is associated with the Piwik open source web analytics platform. It is used to help website owners track visitor behaviour and measure site performance. It is a pattern type cookie, where the prefix \_pk\_id is followed by a short series of numbers and letters, which is believed to be a reference code for the domain setting the cookie. | 1 Years | 2   |
| careers.vodafone.com | \_pk\_ses.{id} | This cookie name is associated with the Piwik open source web analytics platform. It is used to help website owners track visitor behaviour and measure site performance. It is a pattern type cookie, where the prefix \_pk\_ses is followed by a short series of numbers and letters, which is believed to be a reference code for the domain setting the cookie. | 0 Days | 2   |
| linkedin.com | bcookie | This domain is owned by LinkedIn, the business networking platform. It typically acts as a third party host where website owners have placed one of its content sharing buttons in their pages, although its content and services can be embedded in other ways. Although such buttons add functionality to the website they are on, cookies are set regardless of whether or not the visitor has an active Linkedin profile, or agreed to their terms and conditions. For this reason it is classified as a primarily tracking/targeting domain. | 1 Years | 4   |
| linkedin.com | lidc | This domain is owned by LinkedIn, the business networking platform. It typically acts as a third party host where website owners have placed one of its content sharing buttons in their pages, although its content and services can be embedded in other ways. Although such buttons add functionality to the website they are on, cookies are set regardless of whether or not the visitor has an active Linkedin profile, or agreed to their terms and conditions. For this reason it is classified as a primarily tracking/targeting domain. | 1 Days | 4   |
| www.linkedin.com | bscookie | This domain is owned by LinkedIn, the business networking platform. It typically acts as a third party host where website owners have placed one of its content sharing buttons in their pages, although its content and services can be embedded in other ways. Although such buttons add functionality to the website they are on, cookies are set regardless of whether or not the visitor has an active Linkedin profile, or agreed to their terms and conditions. For this reason it is classified as a primarily tracking/targeting domain. | 1 Years | 4   |
| doubleclick.net | IDE | This domain is owned by Doubleclick (Google). The main business activity is: Doubleclick is Googles real time bidding advertising exchange | 1 Years | 4   |
| linkedin.com | li\_gc | This domain is owned by LinkedIn, the business networking platform. It typically acts as a third party host where website owners have placed one of its content sharing buttons in their pages, although its content and services can be embedded in other ways. Although such buttons add functionality to the website they are on, cookies are set regardless of whether or not the visitor has an active Linkedin profile, or agreed to their terms and conditions. For this reason it is classified as a primarily tracking/targeting domain. | 1 Years | 4   |
| youtube.com | VISITOR\_PRIVACY\_METADATA | YouTube is a Google owned platform for hosting and sharing videos. YouTube collects user data through videos embedded in websites, which is aggregated with profile data from other Google services in order to display targeted advertising to web visitors across a broad range of their own and other websites. | 5 Months | 4   |
| youtube.com | VISITOR\_INFO1\_LIVE | This cookie is used as a unique identifier to track viewing of videos | 6 Months | 4   |
| youtube.com | CONSENT | YouTube is a Google owned platform for hosting and sharing videos. YouTube collects user data through videos embedded in websites, which is aggregated with profile data from other Google services in order to display targeted advertising to web visitors across a broad range of their own and other websites. | 1 Years | 4   |
| linkedin.com | li\_sugr | This domain is owned by LinkedIn, the business networking platform. It typically acts as a third party host where website owners have placed one of its content sharing buttons in their pages, although its content and services can be embedded in other ways. Although such buttons add functionality to the website they are on, cookies are set regardless of whether or not the visitor has an active Linkedin profile, or agreed to their terms and conditions. For this reason it is classified as a primarily tracking/targeting domain. | 2 Months | 4   |
| linkedin.com | AnalyticsSyncHistory | This domain is owned by LinkedIn, the business networking platform. It typically acts as a third party host where website owners have placed one of its content sharing buttons in their pages, although its content and services can be embedded in other ways. Although such buttons add functionality to the website they are on, cookies are set regardless of whether or not the visitor has an active Linkedin profile, or agreed to their terms and conditions. For this reason it is classified as a primarily tracking/targeting domain. | 1 Months | 4   |
| demdex.net | demdex | This cookie helps Adobe Audience Manger perform basic functions such as visitor identification, ID synchronization, segmentation, modeling, reporting, etc. | 6 Months | 4   |
| linkedin.com | UserMatchHistory | This domain is owned by LinkedIn, the business networking platform. It typically acts as a third party host where website owners have placed one of its content sharing buttons in their pages, although its content and services can be embedded in other ways. Although such buttons add functionality to the website they are on, cookies are set regardless of whether or not the visitor has an active Linkedin profile, or agreed to their terms and conditions. For this reason it is classified as a primarily tracking/targeting domain. | 1 Months | 4   |
| doubleclick.net | test\_cookie | This domain is owned by Doubleclick (Google). The main business activity is: Doubleclick is Googles real time bidding advertising exchange | 1 Years | 4   |
| youtube.com | YSC | YouTube is a Google owned platform for hosting and sharing videos. YouTube collects user data through videos embedded in websites, which is aggregated with profile data from other Google services in order to display targeted advertising to web visitors across a broad range of their own and other websites. | 0 Days | 4   |
| vodafone.containers.piwik.pro | stg\_externalReferrer | Stores the URL of the site that referred the visitor to your site. | 0 Days | 2   |
| irs.tools.investis.com | AWSALBCORS | AWS - to provide load balancing functionality. | 6 Days | 1   |
| techtarget.com | \_\_cf\_bm | This is a CloudFoundry cookie | 0 Days | 1   |
| irs.tools.investis.com | AWSALB | AWS - to provide load balancing functionality. | 6 Days | 1   |
| www.vodafone.co.uk | SITESJSESSIONID | cookie used for storing user session identifier in web applications | 0 Days | 2   |
| investors.vodafone.com | \_\_CookieConsent | Used to track users consent decision | 0 Days | 1   |
| careers.vodafone.com | stg\_debug | Helps to display your site in debug mode when you use Tag Manager. Only used in site debug mode | 0 Days | 1   |

Controlling your cookies

You can manage your cookie preferences by accessing the preference centre below;

Consent Preferences

You can also manage your cookie preferences in your browser;

You can control how you use cookies in your browser. If you don’t know what browser you’re using, find out by:

* PC users: Go to ‘Help’ in your browser and choosing ‘About’.
* Mac users: Click on the Apple menu and choose ‘About’.

##### **How to check cookies are enabled for PCs**

_Google Chrome_

1. Click the menu button (three horizontal bars) at the top right of your browser window and select ’Settings’ then ‘Show advanced settings…
2. Locate the 'Privacy' heading, and select 'Content settings'
3. Now select 'Allow local data to be set'

_Microsoft Internet Explorer 11_

1. Click on the ‘Settings’ icon (looks like a cog) at the top right of your browser window and select 'Internet options', then click on the 'Privacy' tab
2. Ensure that your Privacy level is set to Medium or below, which will enable cookies in your browser
3. Settings above Medium will disable cookies

_Mozilla Firefox_

1. Click the menu button (three horizontal bars) at the top right of your browser window and select Options
2. Then select the Privacy icon
3. Click on Cookies, then select 'allow sites to set cookies'

##### **How to check cookies are enabled for Macs**

_Safari on OX X_

1. Click on 'Safari' at the top of your browser window and select the 'Preferences' option
2. Click on 'Privacy'
3. Select 'Allow from websites I visit'

##### **Block cookies**

If you'd like to find out how to stop websites using cookies to remember what sites you visit, choose your browser from the list. This will take you to the browser's respective page where you can manage your cookies and site data:

If you change your cookie settings in your browser, your experience with us won't be tracked.

Information on controlling and deleting cookies is also available at [http://allaboutcookies.org](http://allaboutcookies.org/)

#### Vodafone Business - Privacy Portal

### Our strategy in action

No results found

##### Investors

##### Maintaining trust

##### Suppliers

##### Careers

©2024 Vodafone Group

Vodafone Group Plc. Registered Office: Vodafone House. The Connection, Newbury, Berkshire RG14 2FN. Registered in England No 1833679

We use cookies to improve your experience on this site. [Read our policy](https://www.vodafone.com/cookie-policies)
